leapforceathome.com 2013-01-31

# Leapforce About Leapforce

### Privacy Policy

### Scope of the Privacy Policy

This Web site is operated by Leapforce, Inc.

Leapforce understands the importance of our customers' privacy. Our Privacy Policy tells you what information we collect when you visit our Web site, how we use, share and protect it, what choices you have about how the information is used, and how you can access and update that information. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Web site. This Privacy Policy applies to personally identifiable information collected on the Web site where this Privacy Policy is posted. Certain aspects of this Privacy Policy also apply to the personally identifiable information we collect offline.

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, "personally identifiable information" means information that identifies a particular individual, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, and phone number.

## Information Collection

Personally Identifiable Information We Collect

There are many features on this Web site for which no registration is required. However, if you are interested in obtaining information, products or services from Leapforce, or in participating in certain activities on this Web site (such as registering to qualify to become a Leapforce At Home agent), you may need to provide us with information about yourself. For example, if you register to qualify to become an independent agent, we ask for your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number. In addition, we may combine personally identifiable information that you have provided to us with other information that is publicly available or that we receive from other reputable sources.

Other Information Collected Through Technology

In addition to information you choose to provide to us, we also collect non-personally identifiable information through technology to make our site more interesting and useful to you. For instance, when you come to our site, we collect your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. An IP address is often associated with the portal through which you enter the Internet, like your ISP (Internet service provider). Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, we also use IP addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which our visitors visit various parts of our sites. We may combine this information with personally identifiable information that you have provided to us and/or with other information that is publicly available or that we receive from other reputable sources in order to make our Web site and communications more targeted to your interests.

Our Web site also uses cookies. Cookies are small text files that are stored on a user's computer and allow web sites to remember information about users. We use cookies for a variety of purposes in order to enhance the quality of our Web site. We use transient (also called "session ID") cookies to provide continuity from page to page. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We also use persistent cookies. Persistent cookies allow our online store and other parts of our Web site to recognize your browser when you return after your first visit to that part of our Web site. Cookies allow us to personalize your return visits to our site and to save you time during certain activities, such as checking out from our online store. You can choose to remove persistent cookies through your browser options. However, if you do so, your ability to use some areas of our site will be limited, such as our shopping cart feature or online games.

## Information Use

Leapforce may use your personally identifiable information to deliver the products and services that you request, enhance your experience on our site, provide you with informational and/or promotional materials that you might find interesting, and for internal business analysis and other business purposes consistent with this policy. These uses may generally be categorized as relationship maintenance uses and promotional uses. We describe these uses in more detail below.

Relationship Maintenance Uses

Leapforce uses your personally identifiable information to maintain and manage your account, deliver services that you have requested, and generally enhance your experience on our Web site. Collectively, we refer to these types of uses as "Relationship Maintenance Uses," and they include all of the ways in which we use your personally identifiable information to maintain and manage our relationship with you that do not involve sending promotional materials. Examples of Relationship Maintenance Uses include, but are not limited to:

  * Processing and tracking your independent agent qualifications
  * Processing and tracking your profile information
  * Providing the services you request
  * Sending you updates and notices about system updates or outages
  * Sending you other administrative communications
  * Sending you surveys
  * Sending you updates to our privacy policy
  * Making changes to Web-based features

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

We take very seriously our responsibility to maintain your privacy with respect to your personally identifiable information. We will therefore share that information only with the following entities, and only in the manner described below.

Legal Purposes; Business Transactions

Leapforce may disclose any user or customer information, including personally identifiable information, when we believe that doing so is required by law; may be necessary to protect the property, rights, or safety of ourselves, visitors to our Web sites, or other persons. Leapforce may also transfer user or customer information, including personally identifiable information, in connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale.

Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

Leapforce may share with third parties aggregated information about you and other visitors to our Web site. When we do this, however, we make any personally identifiable information non-personally identifiable by combining it with information about other individuals or by removing characteristics that make the information personally identifiable to you. We share this information in order to improve our Web site and develop content and services that we hope will be of interest to you.

## Your Choices

We understand the importance of protecting our customers' privacy, and we therefore provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of having your personally identifiable information used or disclosed for certain purposes.

Leapforce will not share your e-mail address with any third parties.

## Links to Other Sites

We may provide links on our Web site to other sites we think you will enjoy. These sites operate independently of Leapforce and have established their own privacy and security policies. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read these policies at any site you visit.

## Information Security

The security and confidentiality of your information is extremely important to us, and we take a number of steps to safeguard any personally identifiable information that you provide to us. We use data encryption technology to help protect against loss, misuse or alteration of your information. Secure Socket Layers (SSLs) encrypt the information sent between your computer and our database. However, no method of transmitting or storing electronic data is ever completely secure, and therefore we cannot warrant or guarantee that such information will never be accessed, used or released in a manner that is inconsistent with this policy.

## Children's Privacy

Our Web site is not intended for use by any persons under the age of 18 years old, and we do not knowingly collect information about children. We do not sell products or services to children. If you are under 18, you may use this site only with involvement of a parent or guardian.

## Changes in this Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personally identifiable information, we will notify you by sending you an e-mail at the last e-mail address that you provided us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the Web sites covered by this Privacy Policy. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of personally identifiable information that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes.

## Contact Us

If you have questions or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, please write us at:

Leapforce, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy  
7901 Stoneridge Drive #555  
Pleasanton, CA 94588
